newhometab.com 2016-09-07

# HomeTab - Connect your homepage to your mobile phone

Here at One Floor App we value your privacy and believe that transparency and cooperation is the only way to reach our users and provide them with the best service available. In order to allow you more information regarding your rights, and to let you know what and where is made with your information, as well as how we process it, we have set up this privacy policy. 

Please note that while this privacy policy covers the use of our search services, some of our partners and advertisers may have different policies and you should inspect their policies as well. We highly recommend that you check from time whether our policy has changed 

In addition, shall changes the Privacy Policy be made, you as an existing user will be actively notified by displaying a notice associated with the Add on and a link to directly access the Privacy Policy. 

If you choose to contact us via the “Contact Us” page, you may be required to submit some of your personal information, more specially your name and email address. This information will not be stored or use by One Floor App in any way or for any purpose besides replying to your contact request, and s deleted once your reply is sent.

### What Non-Personal Information Is Retained By Widdit?

Non-Personal Information is less sensitive, but may also tell quite a lot about you. Moreover, in some cases, Non-Personal information may be used to deduce more information about you. Widdit protects this information and does not share it without your specific consent. 

Widdit does store some non-personally identifiable information meant for statistical purposes, such as your use of the services, preferences or non-personally identifiable information. Specifically, when you install Widdit's software on your computer, it may retain your IP Address, operating system, installed browser versions, random ID, your recently viewed pages, your usage of the services and other non-identifiable information.

### What do we save on your computer?

In order to identify the computer you are browsing from and provide it with customized services, we store a few cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small text file which contains some information which may only be read by us and contains the following information: (i) your last few searches, (ii) your personal settings, (iii) your country and state and (iv) whether you chose private browsing mode or not. 

### What will we never save?

We value your privacy and try as much as possible to refrain from any activity which may be considered as invasion of your privacy and therefore we will never: (i) use a unique ID on your user, browser or computer for any purpose other than statistical improvement of our services (ii) save or send any password you submit to any website, (iii) operate our services in any HTTPS webpage. 

Every time you browse a webpage, we receive information regarding your visit, the page you are viewing, related keywords and your cookie. Our server sends you personal preferences and information regarding the specific page you are viewing.

### Where is information saved?

We use encryption for information stored on our servers and servers are stored in a secure location. Only a limited number of our employees may access some information, but no employee may access personal information or view your history. Our staff receives periodical instructions regarding privacy, and updates and maintains the servers up to date with software updates and patches. 

### Can you prevent us from saving information?

Yes. 

As we believe that your information is your information, you may request that we will not store any information about you. You may do so by enabling Private Browsing Mode in your browser preferences.

### When is information removed?

We retain information for a short period of time and most information is not retained for more than a year. We only use the information in order to process it to aggregated, non-personally identifiable information and in order to adhere with law enforcement authorities. 

### Who else can see the information?

The information we process may be seen by our business partners, which receive aggregated, non-personally identifiable information regarding his users. Moreover, we process the information to our public domains. 

We may also, in rare cases, share information with our advertisers in cases where there are disputes in regarding to clicks or purchases.

### Who should you contact in case you believe your privacy was violated?

As we highly value your privacy, we appointed a privacy officer which may inquire and investigate any activity in our company and inflict sanctions. Should you believe that your privacy was violated by Protected Search, please contact support@newhometab.com and we shall commence with the inquiry soon. 

One Floor App Ltd   
10 Zarhin St.   
p.o. 3030   
Raanana, Israel
